Class of 1956 Records, 1952-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1956 Records
1952-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1956.
RG 80
3 boxes (1.25 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1956.
Historical Note
The Class of 1956 was the seventy-eighth graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1956 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1956, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1956 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1956 (Box 2202, Folder 1)
- Commencement-Clippings 1956 (Box 2202, Folder 2)
- Commencement-Play, "Uncle Vanya" 1956 (Box 2202, Folder 3)
- Commencement-Speaker, Archibald MacLeish 1956 (Box 2202, Folder 4)
- Freshman Dance 1952 (Box 2202, Folder 5)
- Freshman Handbook 1952-1953 (Box 2202, Folder 6)
- Freshman Rules Test 1952-1953 (Box 2202, Folder 6a)
- Groups 1952-1956 (Box 2202, Folder 7)
- History 1977 (Box 2202, Folder 8)
- Hoop Rolling 1956 (Box 2202, Folder 9)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1956 (Box 2202, Folder 10)
- Junior Prom 1955 (Box 2202, Folder 11)
- Class Letters 1967-1976 (Box 2202, Folder 13)
- Class Letters 1998-2002 (Box 2202, Folder 14)
- Officers-Photographs 1952, 1981 (Box 2202, Folder 15)
- Organization 1956 (Box 2202, Folder 16)
- Poem 1956 (Box 2202, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1966 (Box 2202, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1971 (Box 2202, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1976 (Box 2202, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1981 (Box 2202, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1986 (Box 2202, Folder 21a)
- Reunions 1991 (Box 2202, Folder 21b)
- Reunions 1996 (Box 2202, Folder 21c)
- Rules and Regulations [annotated] 1954-1955 (Box 2202, Folder 21d)
- Songs 1953 (Box 2202, Folder 22)
- Supper 1956 (Box 2202, Folder 23)
- Who's Who 1952 (Box 2202, Folder 24)